easy-share.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy

### In General

Easy-share.com respect the privacy of every individual who visits this website and is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe it is important that you know how we treat the information we receive on the Internet about you. 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Our web server automatically collects certain non-personal information about you when you connect to the Easy-share.com. Examples of this type of non-personal information include the domain names, IP addresses, the type of web browser you are using, and the type of computer operating system you are using. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and other similar information. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to help diagnose problems with our server. The USERAGENT string sent by your web browser which tells us information such as the type of browser and operating system used to access Easy-share.com. 

We will not collect any such personal data from you unless you provide it voluntarily. There are times, however, you may submit information to us, such as your name and a e-mail address. This contact information is used when its necessary to contact with you. 

### Cookies

When you view Easy-share.com, we may store a small text file on your computer. This information is delivered through technology called "cookies". A cookie is a tiny element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. With most web browsers you can block all cookies or delete cookies from your hard drive. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. To learn how perform this functions please consult your browser manual. 

### Links to Other Sites

Our website has links to other sites. When you click a link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

### Policy changes

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice. The policy posted on this website will be the current version dated with the last revision date. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these terms and conditions.
